<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-04-18T09:38:46.387Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-18T09:38:46.387Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix the "Item Not Found" Windows Error When Deleting a File or Folder]]></title>
        <id>62585158ac55f60686c34d0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-solve-item-not-found-windows-error-deleting-file-folder/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T18:32:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use a Windows operating system, then you might have gotten this error before when trying to delete a file or folder.  It happens when, even though the file or folder is there, Windows says that it is failing to delete it because it can't find that file/folder]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Storytelling In UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/use-storytelling-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/use-storytelling-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Storytelling is a powerful tool for any UX designer. It helps create a product and understand the people who use it. In this article, Marli Mesibov takes a real-life example of an app she helped to build in 2017 and explains five steps you can use to help you build a story into your user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marli Mesibov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Kotlin Microservice to AWS with App Runner]]></title>
        <id>624e81ffac55f60686c2f0bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kotlin-aws-app-runner/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone. In this step-by-step tutorial, I would like to show you how to deploy a Kotlin Microservice using Docker and AWS App Runner.  Together, we will learn:  * what exactly is AWS App Runner?   * how to configure AWS Command Line Interface on your local]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Wolak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Inspect an Element – Chrome Shortcut]]></title>
        <id>625807d4ac55f60686c348c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-inspect-an-element-chrome-shortcut/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T01:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Inspect Element feature of the Google Chrome browser is a powerful yet easy-to-use tool. It’s an important part of Chrome Developer Tools that you can use to check the source code of any website. But it doesn’t end there. You can take things further by changing the elements and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infinite Pagination in Flutter with Firebase, Riverpod, and Freeze]]></title>
        <id>6208aaaf56125b0677c64aaa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/infinite-pagination-in-flutter-with-riverpod/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T23:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're developing an app, you'll have to decide how you want to load data. And this will typically bring up the issue of infinite pagination.  You likely won't be showing all of the available items in your DB to your users. You may fetch the first 10-20 items]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rutvik Tak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Azure Static Web Apps to Deploy an Angular App]]></title>
        <id>62549e60ac55f60686c32496</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-azure-static-web-apps-to-deploy-angular-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T23:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI/CD has changed the way IT teams release new software versions.  In this tutorial I'll share my experience with Azure Static Web Apps – Azure's PaaS solution. I'll show you how you can take advantage of its flexibility to deploy an Angular App just by pushing your code to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React 18 New Features – Concurrent Rendering, Automatic Batching, and More]]></title>
        <id>6257472dac55f60686c341a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-18-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T21:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React 18 was released in March 2022. This release focuses on performance improvements and updating the rendering engine.  React 18 sets the foundation for concurrent rendering APIs that future React features will be built on top of.  In this tutorial, I will give a quick guide of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shruti Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python List .append() – How to Add an Item to a List in Python]]></title>
        <id>6257f4fcac55f60686c34755</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-list-append-how-to-add-an-item-to-a-list-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T20:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the most useful and versatile data types available in Python. Lists are a collection of arbitrary objects, just like arrays in other programming languages. In this tutorial you will learn:  * An overview of lists and how they are defined.  * Methods to insert]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write a Script to Change Your Zoom Background Every Day]]></title>
        <id>62563320ac55f60686c3361f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-script-to-change-zoom-background/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T18:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few months, I've found a new use for the pictures that I've taken while hiking. I started using them as Zoom virtual backgrounds.  If you are anything like me and take a lot of pictures, it can be hard to decide which one looks good. And]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saransh Kataria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs Strikethrough – How to Cross Out Text in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>6256dd0eac55f60686c33b09</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/google-docs-strikethrough-how-to-cross-out-text-in-google-docs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T17:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're writing, sometimes you might want to strike through certain text. This means adding a horizontal line that runs through a piece of text.  Here is what it looks like: you are an awesome person.  These are various use cases for strikethroughs:  * To indicate that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Ready for a Job in Tech – Tips for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>62496868ac55f60686c2ccbc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-ready-for-a-job-in-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T17:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months back, I was invited to talk to a group of engineering students of a renowned college in India. I was supposed to interact with them, motivate them, and finally tell them, "What does the industry (the "job" world) look like?", "How can you get ready for it?"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TAPAS ADHIKARY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When And How To Use Freelancers In Your Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/upwork-freelancers-organization/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/upwork-freelancers-organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you work in-house or run a digital agency, there are occasions when you will consider hiring freelancers to supplement your team. Today, we’ll take a look into a platform known as [Upwork](https://upwork.pxf.io/c/1221738/1245573/13634) and the best ways in finding the the right freelancers as well as integrating them into your team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Carousel UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-carousel-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-carousel-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carousels don’t have a good reputation, and rightfully so. But we can make them more useful. **Best practices and guidelines** to improve the carousel design with honest scrolling direction, labels, thumbnails and grouped prev/next-buttons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add a CSS Lens Flare to Photos for a Bright Touch]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364385</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/add-a-css-lens-flare-to-photos-for-a-bright-touch/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T17:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a big fan of movies by J.J. Abrams. I enjoy their tight plots, quippy dialog, and of course: anamorphic lens flares. Filmmakers like Abrams use lens flare to add a dash of ‘homemade’ realism to their movies, …
Add a CSS Lens Flare to Photos for a Bright Touch originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shimin Zhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Around The Artifacts Of Design Systems (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/artifacts-design-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/artifacts-design-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many things, a design system isn’t ever a finished thing — it’s a journey. How we go about that journey can affect the things we produce along the way. Before diving in and starting to plan anything out, be clear about where the benefits and the risks might lie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Donald)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Resource Loading With fetchpriority, a New Priority Hint]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boost-resource-loading-new-priority-hint-fetchpriority/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boost-resource-loading-new-priority-hint-fetchpriority/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new attribute will enable us to fine-tune relative resource priority, improve LCP performance, deprioritize JavaScript fetch calls, and much more. Let’s check out fetchpriority and explore some potential use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Data-Fetching In An Authenticated Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/dynamic-data-fetching-authenticated-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/dynamic-data-fetching-authenticated-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is among the most important things that make up a web application or a conventional native app. We need data to be able to see and perhaps understand the purpose of an application. In this article, we’ll look at another approach to obtaining data in an application that requires authentication or authorization using Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Caleb Olojo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Breadcrumbs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-breadcrumbs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-breadcrumbs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series of articles, we highlight design patterns and techniques to design better interfaces. You can also find more examples in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devs For Ukraine, A Free Online Charity Conference 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/devs-for-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/devs-for-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Devs For Ukraine](https://www.devsforukraine.io/) is a free online charity conference organized by the lovely people at Remote. Two days filled with talks from engineering leaders around the globe, in support of Ukraine. April 25–26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Work Done: Wrangling Stakeholders And Overcoming Obstacles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/stakeholders-overcoming-obstacles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/stakeholders-overcoming-obstacles/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you work in-house or for an external agency, we all share one challenge — dealing with stakeholders, be they your boss, colleagues, or clients. In this post, veteran web designer Paul Boag shares his approach to getting things done in even the most challenging organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding CDN Caching to a Vite Build]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-cdn-caching-to-a-vite-build/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T18:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content delivery networks, or CDNs, allow you to improve the delivery of your website’s static resources, most notably, with CDN caching. They do this by serving your content from edge locations, which are located all over the world. When a …
Adding CDN Caching to a Vite Build originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Progressively Enhanced, Accessible, Filterable And Paginated List]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/accessible-filterable-paginated-list-11ty-alpinejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/accessible-filterable-paginated-list-11ty-alpinejs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how to build a paginated list that works with and without JavaScript? In this article, Manuel explains how you can leverage the power of Progressive Enhancement and do just that with Eleventy and Alpine.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The What, When, Why And How Of Next.js’ New Middleware Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js’ recent 12.0 release included a new beta feature: middleware. For a detailed explanation, you can read all about it in Sam’s previous article, “[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/)”. This article, on the other hand, dives into the overall concept of middleware and how handy it can be in building things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time For Reflection (April 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome the new month with some new wallpapers. Designed with love by artists and designers from across the globe, they are available in versions with and without a calendar for April 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364279</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cut-corners-using-css-mask-and-clip-path-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T16:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently covered creating fancy borders with CSS mask properties, and now we are going to cut the corners with CSS mask and clip-path! A lot of techniques exist to cut different shapes from the corners of any element. …
Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Infinite Scroll]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices and guidelines to improve the UX of infinite scroll with bookmarks, footer reveal and pagination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SmashingConf Is Back In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/smashingconf-workshops-conferences-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/smashingconf-workshops-conferences-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years when almost everything moved online, 2022 marks the return of in-person conferences. In fact, [SmashingConf is back](https://smashingconf.com/conferences): coming to  San Francisco and Austin in June, Freiburg (Germany) in September, and New York in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jarijn Nijkamp)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jobs For Designers And Developers Affected By The War In Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/jobs-designers-developers-war-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/jobs-designers-developers-war-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a designer or developer affected by the war in Ukraine? Here are some options to consider if you’re looking for a design or tech job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Useful Bookmarklets to Boost Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364118</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-development-bookmarklets/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T18:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bookmarklet is a JavaScript-based bookmark that adds to a web browser. I’d like to show you some awesome web browser hacks to aid your web development workflow and how to convert those hacks into time-saving bookmarklets.
Activating design mode
…
6 Useful Bookmarklets to Boost Web Development originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Hover And Pointer Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-hover-pointer-media-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-hover-pointer-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll talk about how to adapt our sites to the different scenarios of a device pointer: whether it has a pointer or not, or how accurate it is. To adapt our site to those devices’ needs we’ll talk about how to properly use media queries `hover`, `pointer`, `any-hover` and `any-pointer`.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remix Routes Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past months, there have been lots of talks dedictaed to Remix. Routing is not only one of the things that sets it apart from other frameworks, but it also fuels great performance and improves the overall experience for developers. Let’s dig in to all  of the features that build up routing in this powerful framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those HTML Attributes You Never Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Louis Lazaris describes and demonstrates some interesting HTML attributes that you may or may not have heard of and perhaps find useful enough to personally use in one of your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Design Is All About Good Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this shorter series of articles, we highlight design patterns, techniques, and strategies to design better digital interfaces. You can also learn much more in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/write-html-the-html-way-not-the-xhtml-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not use XHTML (anymore), but when you write HTML, you may be more influenced by XHTML than you think. You are very likely writing HTML, the XHTML way.
What is the XHTML way of writing HTML, and what …
Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Oliver Meiert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows High Contrast Mode, Forced Colors Mode And CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Properties can be used for far more than just color, and their values update in realtime, both via display mode updates and JavaScript logic. This is powerful stuff. Eric explains how modern CSS is a powerful piece of assistive technology that can thread into it to create flexible, maintainable and adaptive digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>